# Shimrit Breef Ziskand

## Ramat-gan, Israel | 052-6525283



🔼 shimrit021@gmail.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/shimrit-breef-ziskand-261406252



https://github.com/shimritz

I am a recent graduate of a web development bootcamp by Yandex and I'm excited to continue learning how to bring innovative web based solutions to clients. I have knowledge in forex trading and prior working experience as a QA analyst at a financial institution. With the combination of the skills gained at my bootcamp, I'm confident that I can help create quality solutions for any project.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### fullStack developer - internship Qelos

may 2023 - currently

#### SaaS platform for creating SaaS.

 Responsible for delivering e2e features using Vue on the frontend side and NodeJS, Express, and Mongo on the backend side. The work environment included Docker, GitHub, Clickup and CI/CD.

#### Self employment

August 2018 to 2022

- Educational Tutor JAVA Basics QA course.
- Forex trading online platform MT4
- Educational Assistant study material preparation
- Business Assistant schedule and tasks prioritization

## **QA** manual testing

Clalbit, Matrix

January 2015 to August 2018

- E2E tests, testing with QC system: writing and performing manual test cases, Investigated bugs documented in the bug tracking system and worked with the development team to implement fixes.
- SQL, STP, STR

## Agent account manager

## Migdal insurance company

July 2012 to December 2015

- Providing professional guidance to insurance agents
- Analyzing financial reports and solid knowledge in long-term saving pension.

## EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

## **Web Development Program**

**Practicum100 Bootcamp by Yandex** 

10 month intensive online program providing tools and practices to become top-notch Web Developer.

## **QA** Course

John Bryce

2015

## **Bachelor's Degree Bar Ilan University**

Graduated with honours Social Science and Human resources

#### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- HTML & CSS
- JavaScript
- Java
- React
- Vue.js
- MongoDB
- Firebase
- Node.js, Express.js
- Forex trading
- tailwindcss
- QA

## **PROJECTS**

#### **News Explorer:**

Developed a news explorer app that allows users to search for news articles from a variety of sources.

- - https://github.com/shimritz/news-explorer-frontend
  - o https://github.com/shimritz/news-explorer-api
- - o https://news-explorer-frontend-psi.vercel.app/
  - o https://news-explorer-frontend-psi.vercel.app/

#### **Around the US:**

Around The U.S. is an interactive page where users can add, remove, or like photos. This project is created with Reactjs, featuring authorization, registration and REST operations.

- · repo:
  - o https://github.com/shimritz/react-around-api-full
- · website:
  - https://react-around-api-full-pi.vercel.app/signin

#### **Tourdinator:**

Developed a tour organizer app using Reactjs which gather useres who are intersted in joining/orginizing a

· repo: https://github.com/shimritz/tourdinator

## Military Service

2005-2007 - Prime Minister's Office

## LANGUAGES

Hebrew - mother tongue English - fluent